Vince Rosas

246 N Curlew Dr #7107 Mobile: 209.505.860
Ammon, ID rosas.v@att.net

Summary

Recent college graduate, Bachelor's degree in Information Technology, with over 15 years of experience in multiple fields ranging from sales to technical support to telemarketing. Currently learning Python, HTML, and CSS.

Skills

Network Installation and Management | Office365 | Milestone VMS | Genetec VMS | Axis Certified Professional | Cradlepoint Certified Network Professional | Technical Support | Merchandising | Sales | Telemarketing | Connectwise | Zendesk

Selected Work Experience

Installation Manager8/2020-currentIntellisite/EpicIOCeres, Ca

Manage Installation Schedule to ensure Profitability on installation side of the business.

Manage field technicians to reduce cost overruns.

Train field techs on technical aspects of installs to increase productivity and versatility

Manage hardware builders to minimize downtime.

Manage company vehicles and equipment maintenance.

Ensure equipment is properly documented and configured before install

Train new engineers on policies, procedures, and best practices.

Senior Technical Engineer

OPCS/Intellisite

10/2016-8/2020

Ceres. Ca

Installation and configuration of various management systems.

Experience with multiple VMS including Milestone, Genetec, and ExacqVision.

Experienced in camera hardware from Axis, Hikvision, Messoa, and Bosch.

Configuration of networking equipment for security and remote access.

Familiar with Cradlepoint, Cisco, Linksys, Netgear, and Encore.

Responsible for installation and configuration of Windows and Ubuntu on both native and virtual systems.

Required to remote troubleshoot various network, software, and hardware issues

Independent Contractor/Technician1/2008-8/2016Go2ITNorthern California

Networking/Software Installation/Hardware Installation/Technical Support/Customer Service

Residential Sales Representative 4/2014-8/2015 ADT Modesto, Ca **Retail Assistant Manager** 1/2014-3/2014 The Wireless Stores Inc Merced, Ca **Product Pro** 10/2009-3/2013 AT&T Wireless Tracy, CA **Firedog/Product Specialist** 11/2003-3/2009 Circuit City Modesto, Ca

Education

BS - Information Technology with a concentration in Cyber Security, magnu cum laude Manchester, New Hampshire – Online

02/2021